This is Trigun.
Oh, my God.
THE END
Brother, you sure seem like
a mighty prosperous fellow.
What do you want?
I ain't got no cash.
How about buying me a drink, huh?
I'll take anything
that's got alcohol in it.
Ethyl, methyl, cough syrup, whatever.
Screw off, you stupid drunk!
Don't be bringing your raking
corpse in here ever again.
I won't give you alcohol,
but I'd be happy to give you a nice
hot lead bullet between the eyes
So what's the matter?
Are you too scared to talk now, mister?
Don't show your ugly
face around here either.
Those stupid idiots!
So, Meryl, what are we
going to search for today?
A giant man, a red coat, blonde
hair, or a guy with a mohawk?
Let's see now, after that, what was next?
I've had it with rumors.
From now on, I'll only
believe what I see for myself.
There's a gunman out
there that's so amazing,
they put 60 billion double
dollars on his head.
That's where we're going
to begin our search today.
That's awfully vague, Meryl.
Can you be more specific?
All I'm saying is that
we need to pay special
attention to anyone
that might be like that.
But this seems to be such
a peaceful, quiet town.
You've got to always be alert, Millie.
You never know when Vash's stampede is
going to show up and then kaboom. Oh, wow!
Hi, Vash!
Well, hey there!
It's the insurance girls.
Are you working?
Oh, yes. Working hard.
Hmm.
Well, your company must
be very proud of you.
Keep up the good work.
Okay, Mr. Vash, we will.
See you around, ladies.
Gee, Meryl, he matches
the description perfectly.
What makes you think he's Vash?
Well, because he raised his
hand when I called his name.
He only raised his hand
because you called out to him.
It's a natural response when
someone calls out to you.
Listen, we're looking for a horrible
fiend with a price on his head.
Not an obnoxious idiot like that man.
I think I have a cold.
I'm going!
Damn, that really hurt.
Over here, buddy.
Talking to you, pal,
you bump into someone,
then you ain't got nothing
to say for yourself,
huh?
Uh, hi, catch ya later.
Follow this.
Oh, oh, oh, my freaking shoulder hurts
because you slammed into me back there.
How about buying me a drink? Huh?
I don't expect any money here.
I just want you to buy me a drink.
No, no, no, no, no.
Hey, don't be shy.
Hey, we're fouls, aren't we?
Well, I don't even know you!
Come on, Mary! Give her up!
Give her what he's doing to me!
What the...? Stop!
Just run through, bro!
You may want me!
So much capacity here!
That's disgusting. Just ignore them.
But, Mary, wait! Where are you going?
I need your help!
How can you just leave me like this?
How about a little make-up kiss, brother?
Mmm.
Ah!
No!
Hey, bartender, bring me
the best of the house.
You've got money, Frank.
My boy here is the son of
a millionaire. Bring it on!
Nothing but the finest!
He's lying.
Please just bring us the
cheapest in the house, all right?
I don't want nobody making
trouble in here so mister you're
gonna have to let me hold
your gun until you leave huh?
all
right this
is a strange
gun it was given to me I think
it's a pretty good gun no it
isn't yeah you're pretty sharp.
You must know guns.
It's three inches off from only 10 yards.
It wouldn't kill any
more family, would it?
I propose a toast to new friends. Yeah.
Ah, sweet!
Out of all the greatest inventions
man created in our history,
alcohol is its greatest.
Wouldn't you agree, my pal?
By the way,
I wasn't really intending on
buying you drinks, but since I am,
could you listen to my request?
What do you want?
Frank Marlin.
Do you know him?
Uh, never heard of him.
Hey, Grandma!
Oh, I mean, Miss, he is famous, isn't he?
Yeah, he's famous all right.
He's the hero of this here town.
A long time ago, this town was
attacked by vicious bandits.
So Marlon, the gunsmith, went around town?
handing out guns he made himself,
teaching folks how to use
them against the bandits.
Now you know the story.
So what's your business with Frank Marlon?
I just wanted him to fix
my old heap, that's all.
You're wasting your time.
He just pawned it for booze, and
you'd have to buy yourself a new gun.
You really want to give your
gun a complete stranger, mister?
You'll only have yourself to
blame if you get shot in the back.
You'd have to be a damned idiot.
That's right.
Nothing but a hopeless old fool.
What?
Are you serious?
There's really no sheriff in this town?
That's right, Mish.
What do you mean, that's right?
My dear, this is a very quiet town.
Nothing serious ever happens here.
I'm proud to say that Warren
City is a safe place full of
happy people the worst it
ever gets or a few crazy drugs
Mr..
Mayor, I don't mean to alarm you sir,
but there is something very important.
I have to tell you now
The legendary criminal here
in my town, that's ridiculous.
I assure you it's no laughing matter
Well, if he's really that great.
I think it would be kind of fun to have
him attack and spice things up around here
I'm sorry, Mr.
Mayor, but I don't find this funny at all.
Hey!
Big bro!
They was right!
It's just like we heard!
A big armored truck's gonna be
coming to that town's bank at noon!
Excellent, dear brother.
It's 4,000 yards to the next town.
They have no sheriff.
We couldn't ask for a better location.
And listen to this.
I heard a rumor going around.
They say Vash the Stampede
showed up and he's real close.
Do you mean Vash the
Humanoid Typhoon? Yeah.
All right.
I have a plan.
We will have the humanoid typhoon.
There's the stampede
attack the armored car.
I can see it now. This is perfect
Hey,
what'd you do that for
we're just enjoying a drink
your selfish wits G-get me-get
me back my gun, Grandma.
Huh?
What happened, brother?
I don't know.
My head just started to hurt.
That's not good.
I have an idea.
Oh, you have an idea?
Let's go to my place and drink it better.
What are you two doing there?
Oh, it's the insurance girls.
You sure look happy, Mr. Vash.
Having a heck of a good time.
By the way, what are the two
of you doing out so late?
We're here on night patrol.
My partner is convinced that Vash the
Stampede is going to show up in town tonight.
He does not need to know why
we're out so late, Millie.
Sorry about that, Meryl.
Night patrol?
Wow, that's really great!
Aren't these girls wonderful?
Here's to the wonderful women!
I don't think so.
People only drown themselves in alcohol
when they have something
they want to forget.
It's an escape from reality.
Are you still drinking brother?
Yeah, tons.
How about you?
I don't think you're
gonna be in any shape.
I'm gonna work tomorrow.
I gotta cover.
I'm not worried about it.
I only do charity wear. Don't.
get paid, so it doesn't matter
whether I'm coherent or not.
Huh?
My friend, the world is full
of the weak and the suffering.
I've always made it my business to
help out those in time of need. Ah.
But then I found a way to help those
who aren't suffering at y 'all.
What?
What the hell are you talking about?
They say it's wrong to
discriminate, right?
You help someone, and
then someone else suffers.
That is how this world works. Oh.
That is why I've decided to do nothing.
That's all I do, nothing but drink.
There you have equality.
You really think so?
You want to see Frank Marlin?
Might as well give it up, pal.
He just ain't the man he was 10 years ago.
Now he's just a damned
drunk as a gunsmith.
He was something of a genius,
but then in one day his?
His whole life changed when his wife and
kid were killed in a bank robbery, huh?
They happened to be in the
bank at the wrong time.
They just got caught in the crossfire.
But to Frank, the real tragedy was he
had made the guns that the robbers used.
In fact, he had given
them the guns personally.
What the?
Where'd he go?
Oh my god!
Bash the Stampede is here!
He's attacking the armored car!
Bash the Stampede?
It'd be real smart to keep your
distance because this gentleman
here is none other than the
60 billion double dollar man!
Bash the stampede!
The humanoid typhoon!
Leave him alone!
If you get him real mad, he may just
decide to blow this down to smithereens?
Hmm, how pleasant?
Sure, would be nice if all the
townsfolk with this helpful...
uh, excuse me... uh, Mr. Vash?
My name is Meryl Strife and
I'm here with my partner
representing the Bernardelli
Insurance Society.
And well, we were sent here to
shut up and just load the bags!
If only I would have bought
him a box of doughnuts!
Get better!
Get the lead out!
We
will.
I will.
Countermeasure number one.
Take the place of a hostage.
Won't work.
Number two then.
Send everybody into a
mad panic by shouting...
Earthquake!
Even worse.
Well then, what do you suggest?
I have to go with number three. You know,
you just stand back here where it's safe,
let them take the money and shut up.
I don't think so.
Why the hell are you
sticking your neck out?
If you just keep quiet,
you just might stay alive.
There'll be a lot less
damage around here, too.
Look, do you see that little girl? Yeah.
Her mother promised to
buy her something with her
money that used to be in the
bank before this happened.
You know her?
Nah, I just made it up.
What are you doing worrying
about other people's money?
I mean, what good's it gonna do you?
Nothing at all.
Except...
That the situation is not equal.
What's he doing?
What do you think you're doing
trying to play the hero cowboy?
No, not really.
I'm not as great as you might think.
I am.
Ah gee,
that's too bad.
You've got a flat tire.
Well, I guess you won't be escaping in.
How'd he do that?
Are you crazy?
Do you have any idea what you're
getting yourself into, mister?
This gentleman here is the one and
only infamous humanoid typhoon!
He's Vash the Stampede!
Now that's funny.
Pardon me.
But I was under the impression
that he was a lot more handsome.
Are you implying that I
am not Vash the Stampede?
Maybe we should find out.
Huh?
Why?
Why are you doing this?
We can use force if we have to. Right.
Why?
Hold it right there! Huh? Huh?
This gun is an original
Frank Marlin special,
and don't think I'll miss
just cause I'm a woman.
Am I supposed to be afraid
of this Frank Marlin?
It's a Russian piece of crap!
You actually believe you'll
hit me with that thing?
Why?
Why are they doing that?
Why am I just standing here?
That this situation is not equal.
Huh?
What the?
Apparently you think that you have won.
You think wrong!
A piece of parting advice.
You should always save your aces for last.
Checkmate, mister.
Shooting from behind is just not my style.
You'll pay for this!
You will pay!
Wow, they really stick together.
Huh?
Wasn't even loaded.
Sure wasn't.
He's actually dumber than I thought.
That guy is unbelievable.
Here's to all the great
folks to save the town!
In your way!
Grandma, what'd you wait for? Fill her up!
I mean, please fill her up,
miss, if you wouldn't mind.
That's better.
I will never understand him.
Things turned out well after all.
There's no damage to the town.
The chief will probably
give us both promotions.
But the bandit was a fake.
It wasn't really him.
And we still haven't gotten our
chance to meet Vash the Stampede.
But someone matches his description.
Oh, man, I've got to find
the can. Stick him up.
I wouldn't exactly count on this
for everyday use if I were you.
Here, take it.
I've changed the cylinder
to the hammer parts for you.
I gave it a full tune-up.
Hey, thanks.
Oh, heck, you don't need to thank me.
But there is one thing I want to know.
What are you going to do with that gun?
I intend to use it to create equality
and peace throughout the world!
Huh? Huh? Huh?
Well if you ever wear it out again
bring it back I'll fix it as good as new
great when I do I'll Bring the bourbon
next time no thanks I've given up alcohol
I've got better things to do instead
of Drinking what do you think they're
talking about shh you know what I just
realized pal I never did forget your name.
Well, uh, I'm, uh...
You drink too much.
I'm sorry!
Disgusting!
You just don't want to admit that
you're worried about him, do you, Mary?
No, and I'm not following
him for your information.
We just happen to be
going the same direction.
Bang! Bang!
Thank
you
so
much for watching.
He has nothing to do with what we need.
I'm a smile that will be perfect.
It will be perfect for the future.
I'll see you
next time.
Na,
na, na, na, na,
na, na, na.
A past that can't be
forgotten and can't be buried.
A past that can't even be
shaken for just a little time.
The sentiment deep inside each of
their hearts is strong and equal.
For beloved parents and
for a beloved daughter,
two men can only find the answer
from behind their triggers.
The moment the sentimental bullets flew
towards each other, the men stood silent.
Yet were weeping, the past enslaved.